<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Youshitsune</title>
    <link>https://youshitsune.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Youshitsune</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 10:22:32 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://youshitsune.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding Open Source Note Taking</title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/blogs/finding-open-source-note-taking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 10:22:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/blogs/finding-open-source-note-taking/</guid>
      <description>Right now, I&amp;rsquo;m using Obsidian as my note taking app. But, there is only one problem with it and that problem is that it&amp;rsquo;s not open-source. This shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be very concerning, because if you don&amp;rsquo;t use Obsidian Sync feature and save your notes on HDD.
Today, I searched for open-source note taking app like Obsidian. I only found LogSeq which is really great app, but it&amp;rsquo;s not for me really. I like simplicity of Obsidian and when I use LogSeq I really feel that it&amp;rsquo;s cluttered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/about/</guid>
      <description>About Hi, my name is Luka, I live in Serbia and I&amp;rsquo;m 14 years old. I really love programming, linux, basically everything in the world. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact If you want to contact me:
Email: luka@youshitsune.me Discord: JovanovicLuka#1700 Instagram: @jluka1 I&amp;rsquo;m gonna answer you on Discord or Email before than on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/log/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/log/</guid>
      <description>Log 1 Aug, 2022 Today, It was really interesting meeting other devs on KAMACHO discord server. They found it incredible that I code, beacuse I&amp;rsquo;m only 14. I really recommend Open Source Hub discord server (i found it little ironic that server that talks about open-source is on closed-source software), there I met also one guy that&amp;rsquo;s only 13. But, he already has server for helping people with coding. He asked me if I want to join and I replied that I would love to join.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
