<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Youshitsune</title>
    <link>http://example.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Youshitsune</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 06:58:18 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Look What I Found on Tor</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/look-what-i-found-on-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 07:28:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/look-what-i-found-on-tor/</guid>
      <description> Look What I Found on Tor I&amp;rsquo;ve found hacker group with name Rorschach (&amp;lsquo;Watchmen&amp;rsquo;), are they real hacking group or not?
It looks like they took down CP website.
Here is link: http://z4taxzlbse4plf5nckehqvphodwm3jro7qwaqlspz7ez7wylkmrvrtid.onion
Picture of their page: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashing Lineage OS 20 on my Samsung Galaxy A50</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/flashing-custom-rom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:18:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/flashing-custom-rom/</guid>
      <description>Flashing Lineage OS 20 on my Samsung Galaxy A50 I always wanted to flash custom rom on my phone, but there isn&amp;rsquo;t any offical software for it.
So, I started to search for best unoffical options.
I&amp;rsquo;ve found Lineage OS 20 and TWRP.
First try When, I first tried I used heimdall. And soft-bricked my phone.
Second try Then, I found leaked version of odin for linux. I&amp;rsquo;ve flashed everything, and then lineage os was stuck at boot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup SSH Over TOR</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/setup-ssh-over-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 08:54:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/setup-ssh-over-tor/</guid>
      <description>Setup SSH Over TOR This is tutorial for Debian systems.
Setting up Tor - Server First install tor.
sudo apt install tor Then edit torrc file.
sudo vim /etc/tor/torrc Add this to it
HiddenServiceDir /var/lib/tor/hidden-service-example/ HiddenServicePort 22 127.0.0.1:22 HiddenServiceAuthorizeClient stealth hidden-service-example Restart tor
sudo systemctl restart tor That&amp;rsquo;s it for the server
Setting up Tor - Client First install tor.
sudo apt install tor sudo systemctl start tor Then ssh into your machine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local Reality and the CHSH Inequality</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/local-reality-and-the-chsh-inequality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:23:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/local-reality-and-the-chsh-inequality/</guid>
      <description>Local Reality and the CHSH Inequality The CHSH game is a thought experiment involving two parties separated at a great distance (far enough to preclude classical communication at the speed of light), each of whom has access to one half of an entangled two-qubit pair. Analysis of this game shows that no classical local hidden-variable theory can explain the correlations that can result from entanglement. Since this game is indeed physically realizable, this gives strong evidence that classical physics is fundamentally incapable of explaining certain quantum phenomena, at least in a &amp;ldquo;local&amp;rdquo; fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein-Vazirani Algorithm Implementation in Qiskit</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/bernstein-vazirani-algorithm-implementation-in-qiskit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:53:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/bernstein-vazirani-algorithm-implementation-in-qiskit/</guid>
      <description>Bernstein-Vazirani Algorithm Implementation in Qiskit It is a restricted version of the Deutsch-Jozsa algorithm where instead of distinguishing between two different classes of functions, it tries to learn a string encoded in a function.
Here is implementation for Bernstein-Vaziarini algorithm:
from qiskit import * %matplotlib inline from qiskit.tools.visualization import plot_histogram num = &amp;#39;101001&amp;#39; circuit = QuantumCircuit(len(num)+1, len(num)) circuit.h(range(len(num))) circuit.x(len(num)) circuit.h(len(num)) circuit.barrier() &amp;lt;qiskit.circuit.instructionset.InstructionSet at 0x6370a60b4e80&amp;gt; for i, val in enumerate(reversed(num)): if val == &amp;#34;1&amp;#34;: circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting LibreX</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/hosting-librex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 06:50:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/hosting-librex/</guid>
      <description>Hosting LibreX What is LibreX? LibreX is meta-search engine which gives you results from Google, Qwant, Ahmia and popular torrent sites without spying on you. LibreX doesn&amp;rsquo;t save any type of data about the user, there are no logs, no caches.
How to host LibreX in Docker container? To host librex in a Docker container, just use this command:
docker run -d --name librex \ -e TZ=&amp;#34;America/New_York&amp;#34; \ -e CONFIG_GOOGLE_DOMAIN=&amp;#34;com&amp;#34; \ -e CONFIG_GOOGLE_LANGUAGE=&amp;#34;en&amp;#34; \ -p 8080:8080 \ librex/librex:latest How to host LibreX with Docker compose?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Step Closer to Full Suckless</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/going-step-closer-to-full-suckless/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:50:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/going-step-closer-to-full-suckless/</guid>
      <description>Going Step Closer to Full Suckless Today, I was scrolling through suckless rocks page, as every other suckless user. And I saw section for shells, installed yash shell.
I have to admit this is one of the best shells I used. It has functionality like fish shell, but script syntax like bash. Which I really love.
So, that&amp;rsquo;s it. I&amp;rsquo;m one step closer to Full Suckless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Created New Service - RADIANA</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/created-new-service-radiana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 06:50:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/created-new-service-radiana/</guid>
      <description>Created New Service - RADIANA I&amp;rsquo;ve built my own currency system, which you can access at https://rad.youshitsune.tech.
It&amp;rsquo;s open-source, everything is open-source except database.
It&amp;rsquo;s open for registration, if you want some of it just send me mail with title &amp;ldquo;Want Radiana&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring Weechat Proxy to Use Tor</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/configuring-weechat-proxy-to-use-tor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:45:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/configuring-weechat-proxy-to-use-tor/</guid>
      <description>Configuring Weechat Proxy to Use Tor If you are lover of privacy like I am, you&amp;rsquo;ll love this configuration.
TOR Firstly, you need to start tor.
sudo systemctl start tor Then add proxy with this command
/proxy add tor socks5 127.0.0.1 9050 If you want to setup when you connect to any irc server to use proxy, execute this command
/set irc.server_default.proxy &amp;#34;tor&amp;#34; But, if you want for specific server run this</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Look on How to Be Productive</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/my-new-look-on-how-to-be-productive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 20:42:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/my-new-look-on-how-to-be-productive/</guid>
      <description>My New Look on How to Be Productive I&amp;rsquo;ve researched on some ways to be productive(i.e. wasting my damn time). And I completely overlooked the calendar.
Now you should manage your time in blocks. That means for every task you block a time in calendar. One that works for me is Google Calendar, yes I know Google! But I can&amp;rsquo;t found reliable alternative if you&amp;rsquo;ve some alternative mail me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started My Journey on Envs.net</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/started-my-journey-on-envs.net/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 07:46:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/started-my-journey-on-envs.net/</guid>
      <description>Started My Journey on Envs.net I&amp;rsquo;ve started my journey on envs.net. It&amp;rsquo;s minimalistic tilde server. All of my journey updates are going to be here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Set Up My Gemini Capsule</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/ive-set-up-my-gemini-capsule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 16:53:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/ive-set-up-my-gemini-capsule/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve Set Up My Gemini Capsule I&amp;rsquo;ve finally set up my gemini capsule. You can access it at koyu.space/youshitsune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could We Really Be Made of Swiss Cheese?</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/could-we-really-be-made-of-swiss-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:26:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/could-we-really-be-made-of-swiss-cheese/</guid>
      <description>Could We Really Be Made of Swiss Cheese? &amp;ldquo;Could we really be made of Swiss cheese?&amp;rdquo; is paper that explains xenobiology. It&amp;rsquo;s really great introduction to xenobiology. I recommend to read it. PDF
Xenobiology studies life with alternate way to get energy.
Information =&amp;gt; DNA -&amp;gt; Protein Form =&amp;gt; Life as series of innate patterns Metabolism &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Information =&amp;gt; Life as process of chemical transformation of substances Information &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Form =&amp;gt; Life as flow of information Energy&amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Form =&amp;gt; Life as energy flow Metabolism &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Energy =&amp;gt; Life as thermodynamic and kinetic process Xenobiology can provide potential medical and biosafety applications, as well as challenge the foundations of biological engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attention is all you need</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/attention-is-all-you-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:55:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/attention-is-all-you-need/</guid>
      <description>Attention is all you need &amp;ldquo;Attention is all you need&amp;rdquo; is a research paper that proposes a new way of making an AI.
Attention is mapping a query and a set of key-value pairs to an output, all of which are vectors: the query, the keys, and the values. The results are calculated as a weighted sum of the values, ith each value&amp;rsquo;s weight determined by the query&amp;rsquo;s compatibility function with its corresponding key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Matter As A Possible New Energy Source</title>
      <link>http://example.com/blog/dark-matter-possible-new-energy-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:18:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.com/blog/dark-matter-possible-new-energy-source/</guid>
      <description>Dark Matter As A Possible New Energy Source Basically, there is idea for engine: Dark Matter engine uses Dark Matter particles annihilation remnants as propulsion.
Basically, you can have a engine in shape of cube, then you have a high pressure on it. Then just remove one side of cube, place where remnants can exit. Which in result propels the cube.
More about this is written in this paper by Jia Liu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
