<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Youshitsune</title>
    <link>https://youshitsune.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Youshitsune</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 16:53:46 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://youshitsune.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;ve Set Up My Gemini Capsule</title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/2023/ive-set-up-my-gemini-capsule/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 16:53:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/2023/ive-set-up-my-gemini-capsule/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally set up my gemini capsule. You can access it at koyu.space/youshitsune.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Could We Really Be Made of Swiss Cheese?</title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/2023/could-we-really-be-made-of-swiss-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:26:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/2023/could-we-really-be-made-of-swiss-cheese/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Could we really be made of Swiss cheese?&amp;rdquo; is paper that explains xenobiology. It&amp;rsquo;s really great introduction to xenobiology. I recommend to read it. PDF
Xenobiology studies life with alternate way to get energy.
Information =&amp;gt; DNA -&amp;gt; Protein Form =&amp;gt; Life as series of innate patterns Metabolism &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Information =&amp;gt; Life as process of chemical transformation of substances Information &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Form =&amp;gt; Life as flow of information Energy&amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Form =&amp;gt; Life as energy flow Metabolism &amp;lt;-&amp;gt; Energy =&amp;gt; Life as thermodynamic and kinetic process Xenobiology can provide potential medical and biosafety applications, as well as challenge the foundations of biological engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attention is all you need</title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/2023/attention-is-all-you-need/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:55:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/2023/attention-is-all-you-need/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Attention is all you need&amp;rdquo; is a research paper that proposes a new way of making an AI.
Attention is mapping a query and a set of key-value pairs to an output, all of which are vectors: the query, the keys, and the values. The results are calculated as a weighted sum of the values, ith each value&amp;rsquo;s weight determined by the query&amp;rsquo;s compatibility function with its corresponding key.
There are to type of attentions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Matter As A Possible New Energy Source</title>
      <link>https://youshitsune.me/2023/dark-matter-possible-new-energy-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:18:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youshitsune.me/2023/dark-matter-possible-new-energy-source/</guid>
      <description>Basically, there is idea for engine: Dark Matter engine uses Dark Matter particles annihilation remnants as propulsion.
Basically, you can have a engine in shape of cube, then you have a high pressure on it. Then just remove one side of cube, place where remnants can exit. Which in result propels the cube.
More about this is written in this paper by Jia Liu. PDF</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
